- [Instructor] Okay, so now we'll continue
basically creating an endpoint to get a specific player
with an idea, same approach,
some little different nuances,
but in the end it's going to be more the same.
So let's go in the playerControllers.
So we're first going to create the controller.
So I'm going to go ahead and do as we've done in the past,
create a function,
getPlayerWithId.
And again, we're going to do an async function
req, res.
And we're going to try, and then I'm going to again,
copy and paste from the catch like so.
Be careful because when you create a try,
it already has the two curly braces.
So if you also copy that curly brace here,
you're going to have double and you're going to run into an error.
So I'm just going to copy just that.
And then we're going to go ahead
and create the function that's going to connect to Mongoose
and find a player idea.
So let's go ahead and get a new object
with a player and await response from Mongoose.
And we're going to use findByID.
If you start typing find, you're going to find
all the functions that are available through Mongoose.
So in this case, findById.
And what we need in this case is
to pass specific items.
So we need to pass an idea to get the actual player.
So in the params of the request,
we're going to have the PlayerId,
and then basically return like we've done before.
Res.json with a player,
and that's for a controller.
That's basically all we need for the controller.
Then we need to go in the routes and add this route too.
So we're going to again, import it here so the controller
getPlayerWithId,
and then we're going to create a new endpoint for this.
Because this particular endpoint wouldn't work,
'cause we need to pass something in that endpoint
to be able to return player.
So we're going to create a new endpoint altogether,
and this is going to be a new route
with a specific endpoint.
So it's going to be player
and in the paras we're going to pass the PlayerId,
which basically is taken by the controller
and then returning the data.
So we're going to create a get endpoint
and pass the controller, getPlayerWithId like so,
and Get specific player.
And that's basically what we need.
So now if we go into the same example,
we need an id.
So let's go ahead and grab the idea
from the actual database.
So we're going to go in Studio 3T, and I have here my idea.
So what I'm going to do is basically right click here,
copy the value as text, then I'm going to go and Postman.
And what I'm going to do here is not pass
anything in the bot here.
You can pass it in the params if you want,
but in this case I'm going to pass it directly
into the endpoint.
And remember, it's not players.
It's player/ and the id of the player.
So by doing this, I should get the specific player
that I've requested,
and in this case, the first one here that we're seeing.
So if I hit Send,
I got exactly that one player, the object.
So I could use this in the front end at this point
and basically play with this data.
So this completes how
to get a specific player passing an ID into the endpoint.
Let's move on.